<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jackie Gan</title>
    <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jackie Gan</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jackiegan.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 13:16:52 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jackiegan.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python and Pipenv</title>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/pythonandpipenv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 13:16:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackiegan.com/posts/pythonandpipenv/</guid>
      <description>Python is a great language for everyone. Easy to understand, and a lot of libraries to mess around with.
However, managing packages in python can be a pain. Also, installing it the right way.
I had to personally witness this myself&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. Installing Python (on macOS) I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of brew, brew is a Package Manager for macOS (something like apt-get in linux).
Open terminal and run this command to install homebrew /bin/bash -c &amp;#34;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim</title>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 11:37:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackiegan.com/posts/vim/</guid>
      <description>Learning vim(neovim) from the goat himself, ThePrimeagen.
Vim As Your Editor (1/6): The Basic Vim Movements
j moving down k moving up h moving left l moving right w moving forward of a word b moving backward of a word &amp;ldquo;try not to rely on your arrow keys&amp;rdquo; yy yank the line(copy it), store in the register p paste the line dd delete the line u undo the line when you want to delete a function, dd + dd + dd isn&amp;rsquo;t practical shift + v visual line mode(highlights the line), in this mode you can use jk or other commands from above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel pt1</title>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 20:34:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackiegan.com/posts/travel/</guid>
      <description>In the last few years, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been traveling internationally or domestically due to the unspoken deadly disease 😷. In this travel pt1, I want to share some of my favorite places that I have traveled before the pandemic and places I have traveled this summer.
Atlanta, GA (ATL) I have to admit I had a great time at Atlanta with friends. There is a lot to the city, a lot of places to visit such as Atlanta Botanical Garden, World of Coca-Cola, Georgia Aquarium and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Coursework</title>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/coursework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackiegan.com/posts/coursework/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science &amp;amp; Mathematics bulletin
Spring 2023 (TBA credits) More Graduate Courses coming Enrolled in 4+1 program Fall 2022 (17 credits) KINS 1009 - Backpacking and Camping I Instructor: Richard M. Stein MATH 3096 - Introduction to Modern Algebra Instructor: Maria Lorenz CIS 4397 - Independent Research in Computer Science Instructor: Yu Wang MATH 3031 - Probability Theory I Instructor: Wei-Shih Yang CIS 5526 - Machine Learning (Graduate Course) Instructor: Slobodan Vucetic CIS 5511 - Programming Techniques (Graduate Course) Instructor: Alex Pang Spring 2022 (18 credits) MATH 3044 - Numerical Analysis II Instructor: Qingguang Guan MATH 2111 - Basic Concepts of Math Instructor: Charles Osborne CIS 4282 - Independent Study Instructor: Yu Wang MUST 0809 - World Musics &amp;amp; Cultures (ETS) Instructor: Marion Jacob IH 0851 - Intellectual Heritage I: The Good Life (ETS) Instructor: Maria Ponce De Leon IH 0852 - Intellectual Heritage II: The Common Good Instructor: David Mislin Fall 2021 (12 credits) CIS 3207 - Introduction to Systems Programming &amp;amp; Operating Systems Instructor: Gene Kwatny MATH 3043 - Numerical Analysis I Instructor: Qingguang Guan Lab: Jacob S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://jackiegan.com/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackiegan.com/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!
We all start from somewhere! :))</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
